A Finding Aid to the Dorothy Weiss Gallery Records, circa 1964-2001 (bulk 1984-2000), in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Artist Files, circa 1964-2001; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 17.5 Linear feet Boxes 1-18, OV 21
  - Tsang, Re-Cheng, General, circa 1997-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Tsutsumi, Nobuko, General, 1994-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Includes slides of Tsutsumi.
  - Turner, Robert, Archival Resource Key (Box 14)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 13-14)
    - Printed Material, 1979-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 15-16)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1980-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Unterseher, Chris, General, 1981-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Van Cline, Mary, General, circa 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Van Eimeren, Eric, General, circa 1997-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Van Nostrand, General, circa 1995-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Vikova, Jindra, General, circa 1990-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Walker, Jamie, Archival Resource Key (Box 14)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, DW Gallery, 1984-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1982-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 24-25)
    - Printed Material, 1984-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Photograph of Walker, circa 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 28-31)
  - Warashina, Patti, Printed Material, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Watkins, James, Archival Resource Key (Box 14)
    - General, 1985-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1990-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Weber, Mike, General, 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Weiss, Dick, General, 1996-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Welsh, Stan, Archival Resource Key (Box 14)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, DW Gallery, 1984-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Printed Material, 1985-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1984-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Williams, Neil, Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - General, 1983-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Photograph of Williams?, 1990?; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1983-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Winkler, Allan, Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - General, 1981-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Photographs of Winkler, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1981-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Wolf (Wärff), Ann, General, 1989-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Wolkow, Lisa, General, circa 1986-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Won, Kyung Hwan, General, circa 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Won Lee, Jae, General, circa 1994-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Wood, Beatrice, General, 1989, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Wyner, Sandra, General, 1981-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Young, Sara, General, 1985, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Yuh, Sun-Koo, General, 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Zimmerman, Arnold, General, 1984-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Slides, Archival Resource Key (Box 16)
    - Abilgard, Mark, circa 1988-1999; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 1) (Box 16)
    - Adams, Hank Murta, circa 1980-1989; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 1) (Box 16)
    - Aebersold, Jane Ford, circa 1982-1987; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 1-2) (Box 16)
    - Anderson, Daniel, 1989-1994; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 2) (Box 16)
    - Autio, Rudy, circa 1975-1997; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 2-3) (Box 16)
    - Berman, Harriete Estel, circa 1982-1991; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 3) (Box 16)
    - Blakely, Ellen, circa 1982-1986; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 3-4) (Box 16)
    - Brice, Daniel, circa 1994-1999; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 4) (Box 16)
    - Castle, Wendell, circa 1988-1996; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 4) (Box 16)
    - Chamberlin, Scott, circa 1981-2000; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 4-5) (Box 16)
    - Christenson, Ann, circa 1990-1997; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 5) (Box 16)
    - Clayman, Daniel, circa 1987-1989; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 5) (Box 16)
    - Corcoran, Annette, 1981-1998; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 6-7) (Box 16)
    - Cornelius, Philip, circa 1981-1999; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 7) (Box 16)
    - Cox, Kris, circa 1989-1995; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 7) (Box 16)
    - de la Torre, Einar and Jamex, undated; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 8) (Box 16)
    - de Swart, Peter, 1989-1995; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 8) (Box 16)
    - Dickey, Kim, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 8) (Box 16)
    - Di Pasqua, Paul, 1989-1993; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 8) (Box 16)
    - Duckworth, Ruth, circa 1976-1994; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 8-9) (Box 16)
    - Earl, Jack, circa 1987-1996; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 9) (Box 16)
    - Ennis, Elizabeth, circa 1994-1997; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 9) (Box 16)
    - Eslick, Susan, circa 1980; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 9) (Box 16)
    - Federighi, Christine, circa 1979-1984; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 9-10) (Box 16)
    - Fletcher, Sean A., 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 10) (Box 16)
    - Frey, Barbara L., circa 1990-1994; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 10) (Box 16)
    - Fritz, Donald C., circa 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 10) (Box 16)
    - Furman, David, circa 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 10-11) (Box 16)
    - Gill, John, circa 1981-1994; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 11) (Box 16)
    - Hafner, Dorothy, circa 1980-1986; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 11) (Box 16)
    - Heikoop, Govert, 1995-1998; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 11) (Box 16)
    - Hepburn, Tony, circa 1978-1994; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 12) (Box 16)
    - Hilferty, Patrick, circa 1990-1997; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 12) (Box 16)
    - Hobson, Charles, circa 1990-1997; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 12-13) (Box 16)
    - Huff, Jason, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 13) (Box 16)
    - Irwin, Jeff, circa 1992-1997; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 13) (Box 16)
    - Isupov, Sergei, circa 1996-2000; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 13) (Box 16)
    - Iwata, Kiyomi, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 13) (Box 16)
    - Jacques, Frank, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 13-14) (Box 16)
    - Kaneko, Jun, 1982-1998; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 14) (Box 16)
    - Kehlmann, Robert, circa 1989-1992; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 14 (Box 16)
    - Koblitz, Karen, 1980-1985; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 14) (Box 16)
    - Koblitz, Karen, 1980-1985; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 15) (Box 17)
    - Kovatch, Ron, circa 1987-1989; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 15) (Box 17)
    - Krusoe, Sana, circa 1985-1993; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 15) (Box 17)
    - LaBianca, Lawrence, circa 1992-1999; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 15-16) (Box 17)
    - Lancet, Mark, circa 1994-1997; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 16) (Box 17)
    - Lastomirsky, Geo, 1989-1998; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 16) (Box 17)
    - Leedy, Jim, circa 1986-1993; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 16) (Box 17)
    - Lindquist, Mark, 1989-1992; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 16-17) (Box 17)
    - Lucero, Michael, circa 1981-1999; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 17) (Box 17)
    - Mace, Flora and Joey Kirkpatrick, circa 1989; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 17) (Box 17)
    - Mangus, Kirk, circa 1979-1997; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 17-18) (Box 17)
    - Marak, Louis, 1980-1989; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 18) (Box 17)
    - Marioni, Paul, circa 1987-1998; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 18) (Box 17)
    - Marquis, Richard, circa 1978-1998; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 18) (Box 17)
    - Massaro, Karen, circa 1994-1999; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 18) (Box 17)
    - Mathieu, Paul, circa 1984-1990; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 19) (Box 17)
    - Matthews, Kazuko Kayasuga, circa 1983-1992; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 19) (Box 17)
    - Matuszewski, Gloria, circa 1993-1997; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 19) (Box 17)
    - Mayeri, Beverly, circa 1978-1999; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 19-20) (Box 17)
    - McBride, Kathryn, circa 1984-1999; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 20) (Box 17)
    - Milnes, Robert, circa 1989-1998; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 20) (Box 17)
    - Miyata, Masako, circa 1983-1997; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 20) (Box 17)
    - Mizuno, Keisuke, circa 1997-1999; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 20) (Box 17)
    - Montgomery, Steven, circa 1996-1999; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 21) (Box 17)
    - Morris, James, circa 1983-1996; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 21) (Box 17)
    - Morris, William, circa 1989-1997; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 21) (Box 17)
    - Mosman, Timothy, circa 1987-1989; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 21) (Box 17)
    - Musler, Jay, circa 1983-1998; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 21-22) (Box 17)
    - Olivier, Diane, circa 1984-1991; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 22) (Box 17)
    - Patti, Thomas, circa 1977-1984; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 22) (Box 17)
    - Pearson, Todd, circa 1984-1994; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 22) (Box 17)
    - Peet, Anne, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 22) (Box 17)
    - Perkins, Flo, circa 1980-1989; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 23) (Box 17)
    - Podmore, Amy, circa 1984-1998; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 23) (Box 17)
    - Popelka, Jeremy, circa 1994-1996; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 23) (Box 17)
    - Powers, Pike, circa 1989-1994; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 24) (Box 17)
    - Quinn, Jeanne, circa 1997-1999; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 24) (Box 17)
    - Rainey, Clifford, circa 1993-1997; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 24) (Box 17)
    - Reitz, Donald, 1989; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 24) (Box 17)
    - Rice, Jacqueline, circa 1982-1990; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 24-25) (Box 17)
    - Ritchie, Gail, circa 1981-1995; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 25) (Box 17)
    - Roberts, Amy, circa 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 25) (Box 17)
    - Roberts, Gregory, circa 1991-1998; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 25) (Box 17)
    - Rohlfing, John G., circa 1985-1997; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 25-26) (Box 17)
    - Rosdol, Leslie, circa 1987-1995; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 26) (Box 17)
    - Samios, William, circa 1994-1998; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 26) (Box 17)
    - Sasaki, Hitoshi, circa 1982-1986; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 26) (Box 17)
    - Savage, Juta, circa 1985-1990; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 26) (Box 17)
    - Scanga, Italo, circa 1981-1996; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 26-27) (Box 17)
    - Schacter, Mayer, circa 1984; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 27) (Box 17)
    - Scoon, Thomas, circa 1989, 1992; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 27) (Box 17)
    - Sedestrom, Robert, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 27) (Box 17)
    - Shay, Robert, circa 1983-1988; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 27) (Box 17)
    - Silliman, Christopher, circa 1989-1998; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 27-28) (Box 17)
    - Simon, Sandy, circa 1986-1997; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 28) (Box 17)
    - Slusky, Joe, circa 1969-1990; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 28) (Box 17)
    - Smith, Barbara Bell, circa 1984-1991; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 28) (Box 17)
    - Sperry, Robert, circa 1981-1991; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 28) (Box 17)
    - Statom, Therman, circa 1988-1999; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 28) (Box 17)
    - Stern, Melissa, circa 1985-1987; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 28) (Box 17)
    - Stewart, William, circa 1994-1998; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 28-29) (Box 17)
    - Strasser, Dharma, circa 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 29) (Box 17)
    - Sugiyama, Michio, circa 1983-1991; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 29) (Box 17)
    - Takayama-Ogawa, Joan, circa 1991-1997; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 29) (Box 17)
    - Tarantino, Claudia, circa 1994-1999; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 29) (Box 17)
    - Taylor, Yoshio, circa 1983-1993; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 29) (Box 17)
    - Terestman, Julie, circa 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 29) (Box 17)
    - Thayer, Susan, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 29) (Box 17)
    - Tsutsumi, Nobuko, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 29-30) (Box 17)
    - Turner, Robert, circa 1985-1991; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 30) (Box 17)
    - Walker, Jamie, circa 1983-1999; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 30) (Box 17)
    - Watkins, James, circa 1982-1986; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 30) (Box 17)
    - Williams, Neil, circa 1980-1992; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 30) (Box 17)
    - Young, Sara, circa 1988-1991; Archival Resource Key; (slide box 30) (Box 17)
    - Slide Transparency Duplicates, Archival Resource Key (Box 18)
  - Oversized Artist Files, Archival Resource Key (Box OV 21)
    Includes files on Tony Hepburn, William Hunt, and Kiyomi Iwata.
- Exhibition Files, 1979-1999; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 0.75 Linear feet Box 19
  This series contains records of approximately twenty-five group exhibitions held at the gallery. Files typically contain announcements, press releases, correspondence with participating artists, price lists, and photographs of artwork. Researchers should note that records of other exhibitions can be found in the artist files.
  For several exhibitions, such as the Alfred Show (1989), and some of the New Glass exhibitions and Teapot Invitationals, Weiss requested that participants submit black and white sketches, rather than photographs of artwork, for the exhibition announcements. She asked that the sketches "suggest the character and spirit of the work" to be included in the exhibition. Many of these original black and white drawings, with accompanying letters from the artists, can be found in this series. One oversized letter with accompanying teapot drawings by Juta Savage, is housed in Series 1: Artist Files, and can be found in OV 21.
  See Appendix for a list of exhibitions at Meyer Breir Weiss Contemporary Crafts, Inc., and the Dorothy Weiss Gallery.
  Files are chronologically by date of exhibition which appears in parentheses after the title and is followed by span dates for the folder. Some files contain records of several exhibitions of the same title over a period of years, for which no specific exhibition years are given. These folders are placed at the beginning of the series. Within folders, material is generally arranged chronologically. However, in cases where the gallery collected records relating to individual artists in a single exhibition, material is arranged alphabetically by artist and then chronologically.
  Appendix: List of Exhibitions at Meyer Breir Weiss Contemporary Crafts, Inc., and the Dorothy Weiss Gallery
  Below is a list of exhibitions held at Meyer Breir Weiss Contemporary Crafts, Inc., and the Dorothy Weiss Gallery from 1980 to 2000. Italics indicate the actual title of the exhibition. Every effort has been made to include all known exhibitions.
  Date Exhibition
  Oct. 14-Nov. 15, 1980 David Kuraoka - Clay
  Nov. 18-Dec. 24, 1980 Functional Forms
  Mar. 17-Apr. 11, 1981 New Forms in Glass, Series I
  Apr. 14-May 9, 1981 New Forms in Glass, Series II
  May 12-June 6, 1981 New Forms in Glass, Series III
  Sept. 15-Oct. 17, 1981 Joyce Kohl - Clay Sculpture; Gayle Luchessa - Felting
  Apr. 6-May 15, 1982 David Gilhooly
  May 25-June 26, 1982 Philip Cornelius
  July 6-Aug. 7, 1982 Painted Object
  Mar. 1-Apr. 2, 1983 Buildings
  Apr. 5-May 14, 1983 Teapots
  May 31-July 9, 1983 Neil Williams - An Explanation of the Vessel
  July 30-Sept. 3, 1983 David Gilhooly
  Feb. 7-Mar. 3, 1984 Roseline Delisle - Porcelain; Walter Lieberman - Glass
  Apr. 3-28, 1984 Jay Kvapil, Sculpture - Domestic Monuments Series
  May 1-June 2, 1984 Stan Welsh, Recent Works - Ceramic Sculpture and Monotypes
  Aug. 30-Sept. 22, 1984 Philip Cornelius - New Work, Porcelain Vessels
  Sept. 25-Oct. 27, 1984 Jamie Walker - Ceramic Work and Installation
  Nov. 1-24, 1984 Yoshio Taylor - Clay Sculpture
  Nov. 28-Dec. 31, 1984 The Teapot
  Feb. 5-Mar. 2, 1985 Neil Williams - Recent Work in Clay
  Mar. 5-30, 1985 Scott Chamberlin - New Clay Sculpture
  Apr. 2-27, 1985 Hank Murta Adams - Glass Sculpture
  Apr. 30-Jun. 1, 1985 Allan Winkler - Figurative Ceramic Sculpture and Paper Cut-outs
  June 6-July 6, 1985 Glass Sculpture - Five Artists
  July 12-Aug. 4, 1985 Group show
  Aug. 6-31, 1985 Linda Einfalt - Sculpture; Tom Heid - Ceramic Sculpture
  Aug. 8-Sept. 1, 1985 Jamie Walker
  Sept. 5-28, 1985 Louis Marak, Kazuko Matthews - Ceramic Sculpture
  Sept. 15-29, 1985 Philip Cornelius
  Oct. 3-Nov. 2, 1985 Rudy Autio - Ceramic Sculpture
  Nov. 5-30, 1985 Juta Savage - Recent Work, Sculpture and Porcelain
  Dec. 5-Jan. 4, 1985-86 Roseline Delisle - Recent Work in Porcelain and Drawings
  Feb. 6-28, 1986 British Ceramics
  Mar. 6-29, 1986 Jamie Walker - Ceramic Work
  April, 1986 Jay Kvapil - Sculpture
  April, 1986 Hitoshi Sasaki - Wall Sculptures
  Apr. 29-May 31, 1986 Rick Dillingham - Recent Work
  June 3-July 5, 1986 Stan Welsh - Ceramic Sculpture, Monotypes
  June 11-July 4, 1986 Hank Murta Adams - Sculpture
  July 12-Aug. 2, 1986 Barbara Bell Smith - Paintings
  Sept. 11-Oct. 4, 1986 Philip Cornelius - Porcelain Vessels
  Oct. 9-Nov. 1, 1986 Tony Hepburn - New Sculpture
  Nov. 5-29, 1986 Yoshio Taylor - Figurative Sculpture
  Dec. 2-Jan. 3, 1986-87 Teapots - New Boundaries
  Jan. 8-31, 1987 Todd Pearson - New Sculpture
  Feb. 5-28, 1987 Jack Bowers - New Boxes
  Mar. 3-28, 1987 Louis Marak - New Sculpture
  Mar. 31-Apr. 25, 1987 Scott Chamberlin - "A Different Garden," Sculpture and Drawings
  Apr. 30-May 23, 1987 Robert Turner
  May 26-June 9, 1987 Amy Podmore - Figurative Sculpture
  June 11-July 8, 1987 Hank Murta Adams - Sculpture, Glass and Bronze
  June 11-Aug. 8, 1987 Introductions - Amy Podmore, Michio Sugiyama
  Aug. 11-Sept. 5, 1987 Diane Olivier - Drawings
  Sept., 1987 Nancy Carman
  Oct. 8-31, 1987 Rudy Autio - Ceramic Sculpture
  Nov. 5-28, 1987 Roseline Delisle - New Work
  Dec., 1987 Group Glass Exhibition
  Jan. 7-30, 1988 Joseph Slusky - New Sculpture
  Feb. 2-Feb. 27, 1988 Linda Einfalt, Jaap Bongers - Recent Sculpture
  Feb. 5-Mar. 28, 1998 Potent Images - Figurative Clay Sculpture
  Mar. 3-Apr. 2, 1988 Tony Hepburn - Recent Sculpture and Drawings
  Apr. 7-30, 1988 Jamie Walker - New Work
  May 5-28, 1988 Stan Welsh - New Sculpture
  June 9-July 2, 1988 Philip Cornelius - New Work
  July 5-30, 1988 Introductions: Tim Mosman - Sculpture and Paintings; Marc Pandone - Drawings
  Aug. 4-Sept. 3, 1988 Allan Winkler - Figurative Ceramic Sculpture and Paper Cut-outs
  Sept. 8-Oct. 1, 1988 Barbara Bell Smith - New Paintings
  Oct. 6-29, 1988 Jun Kaneko - New Work
  Nov. 3-26, 1988 Yoshio Taylor - New Ceramic Sculpture
  Dec. 1-Jan. 7, 1989 Annette Corcoran - New Work
  Jan. 5-31, 1989 1989 - New Work for the New Year
  Feb. 2-28, 1989 Diane Olivier - New Drawings
  Mar. 2-Apr. 1, 1989 Amy Podmore - Recent Work
  Apr. 6-May 3, 1989 Ruth Duckworth - New Work
  May 4-31, 1989 The Alfred Show - Professors and Graduates Associated with Alfred University
  June 8-July 6, 1989 Hank Murta Adams - Sculpture
  July 8-Aug. 1, 1989 Introductions 1989: Deborah Hoch - Narrative Clay; Lisa Reinertson - Figurative Ceramic Sculpture
  Sept. 7-Oct. 3, 1989 Scott Chamberlin - New Sculpture
  Oct. 5-31, 1989 Rudy Autio - New Sculpture
  Nov. 2-Dec. 2, 1989 James Morris - Narrative Sculpture
  Dec. 7-30, 1989 New Glass
  Jan. 4-27, 1990 1990 - New Work for the New Year by Gallery Artists
  Feb. 1-27, 1990 Louis Marak - New Work
  Mar. 1-31, 1990 Beverly Mayeri - New Sculpture
  Apr. 5-28, 1990 John Gill - New Work
  May 3-June 30, 1990 Jack Earl - Narrative Sculpture
  July 5-Aug. 5, 1990 Steve Briscoe - Introductions
  Aug. 9-Sept. 1, 1990 Teapot Invitational
  Sept. 6-Oct. 6, 1990 Jamie Walker - New Work
  Oct. 11-Nov. 3, 1990 Jun Kaneko - New Sculpture
  Nov. 8-Dec. 1, 1990 Tony Hepburn - Recent Sculpture
  Dec. 6-31, 1990 Annette Corcoran - New Work
  Jan. 10-Feb. 2, 1991 Sculpture 1991
  Feb. 7-Mar. 2, 1991 Stan Welsh - New Work
  Mar. 7-30, 1991 Yoshio Taylor - New Sculpture
  Apr. 4-27, 1991 Barbara Bell Smith - Recent Paintings
  May 2-June 1, 1991 Michael Lucero - New Work
  June 6-29, 1991 New Sculpture - Hank Murta Adams, Pike Powers, Michael Scheiner, James Watkins
  July 3-27, 1991 Introductions '91: Jeremy Popelka - Glass Sculpture; Sana Krusoe - Ceramic Sculpture
  Aug. 1-31, 1991 New Glass
  Sept. 5-28, 1991 Diane Olivier - Works on Paper
  Oct. 3-Nov. 2, 1991 Robert Turner - Master Works in Clay
  Nov. 7-30, 1991 James Morris - New Sculpture and Drawings
  Dec. 5-Jan. 11, 1991-92 Teapot Invitational
  Feb. 6-29, 1992 John Gill - New Sculpture
  Mar. 5-28, 1992 Beveryly Mayeri - New Ceramic Sculpture
  Apr. 2-May 2, 1992 Hank Murta Adams - Glass Sculpture
  May 7-30, 1992 Ruth Duckworth - Recent Work
  June 4-27, 1992 Jack Earl - New Narrative Sculpture
  July 2-Aug. 1, 1992 Introductions
  Aug. 6-29, 1992 Therman Statom - New Sculpture, Glass Houses, Ladders, and Wall Pieces
  Sept. 3-26, 1992 Jamie Walker - New Sculpture
  Oct. 1-31, 1992 Jun Kaneko - Recent Sculpture
  Nov. 5-28, 1992 Tony Hepburn - Recent Sculpture and Drawings
  Dec. 3-Jan. 2, 1992-93 Annette Corcoran - Figurative Teapots
  Dec. 5-Jan. 11, 1992-93 Teapot Invitational
  Jan. 7-39, 1993 Robert Kehlmann - Drawings with Glass
  Feb. 4-27, 1993 The Clay Figure
  March 4-27, 1993 Glass Invitational
  Apr. 1-May 1, 1993 James Morris - Ceramic Sculpture, Paintings and Drawings
  May 6-29, 1993 Teapot Invitational
  June 3-July 3, 1993 Hank Murta Adams - Sculpture
  July 10-31, 1993 Introductions '93 - Daniel Goldstein, Metal Sculpture with Movement and Light
  Sept. 9-Oct. 2, 1993 Robin Grebe, James Watkins - Recent Works in Glass
  Oct. 7-30, 1993 Recent Sculpture - Rudy Autio, Jim Leedy
  Nov. 4-27, 1993 Mark Lindquist - Recent Works
  Dec. 2-Jan. 29, 1993-94 Clifford Rainey - New Sculpture, Drawings and Installation
  Feb. 3-26, 1994 Clay Selections
  Mar. 3-Apr. 2, 1994 Glass Invitational
  Apr. 7-30, 1994 Beverly Mayeri - New Sculpture
  May 5-28, 1994 William Morris - New Sculpture
  June 2-July 2, 1994 John Gill, Louis Marak - Recent Work
  July 7-30, 1994 Introductions '94 - Lawrence LaBianca, Gregory Roberts
  Aug. 4-27, 1994 Teapot Invitational
  Sept. 8-Oct 1, 1994 Ruth Duckworth - Recent Sculpture
  Oct. 6-29, 1994 Michael Lucero - Dogs and Children
  Nov. 3-26, 1994 Jun Kaneko - Recent Work
  Dec. 1-Jan. 7, 1994-95 Annette Corcoran - New Work, A Bird in the Hand
  Jan. 14-Feb. 25, 1995 Therman Statom - Northern Tide - Site-Specific Installation and Other Works
  Mar. 2-Apr. 1, 1995 Stan Welsh - New Work
  Apr. 6-29, 1995 Daniel Brice, David Tomb - Recent Drawings